<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-02-25T09:12:26+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tetsu’s Blog</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>Shoto</name></author><entry><title type="html">Back after a short hiatus</title><link href="/entry/6" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Back after a short hiatus" /><published>2021-02-23T06:54:15+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-23T06:54:15+00:00</updated><id>/entry/6</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/6">&lt;p&gt;Good afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;After an unexpected hiatus, I am finally able to write a blog post again. So today I will tell you what happened to me / what I worked on the past week.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;hr /&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;1. Adding a search function on my blog&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Even though I am gonna the blog's skin soon, I still took the chance to add a search function to the current blog skin, since I have been wanting to add it for a long time, and people might use the skin for their own blogs.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/christian-fei/Simple-Jekyll-Search&quot;&gt;Simple Jekyll Search&lt;/a&gt; in order to implement the search function.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;2. Hosting my first avatar collab in Discord&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;One of my goals was to host avatar collabs in Discord, since I wanted to improve my skills on editing images. The main theme of the collab was hololive&lt;a href=&quot;#about-hl&quot;&gt;*&lt;/a&gt; ~ nonstop story. Since I did everything related to image editing on my mobile, there were only 23 slots in the collab. 19 of the slots were filled, which I'm kinda proud of since this is the first collab I have hosted.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p id=&quot;about-hl&quot;&gt;*Hololive Production is a virtual YouTuber talent agency owned by Japanese company Cover Corp. and formed in December 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;figure class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.ppy.sh/9cf8b38d32116d22a739277591ffbb3539dcfcde/68747470733a2f2f692e696d6775722e636f6d2f3345796c4e5a322e6a7067&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.ppy.sh/9cf8b38d32116d22a739277591ffbb3539dcfcde/68747470733a2f2f692e696d6775722e636f6d2f3345796c4e5a322e6a7067&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;The image I used in the collab&lt;/figcaption&gt;
        &lt;/figure&gt;
        &lt;hr /&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;These are all the things that occured last week. For now, I am currently organizing another collab based on Genshin Impact, while I'm also planning to release a new blog skin.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Diary" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Blog upgrade</title><link href="/entry/5" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Blog upgrade" /><published>2021-02-11T10:50:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-11T10:50:00+00:00</updated><id>/entry/5</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/5">&lt;p&gt;Good evening.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;After a few days of working on the new skin, I have finished making it.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Like the previous blog skin, it was based on a skin from Blog Naver, with a few changes on it. I never got the chance to finish the previous skin because I was too lazy and that it's too plain, which is why I created a new one instead.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;However, unlike the previous one, this new skin took more than 1 day to make due to how hard it is to style it properly, mostly since the new blog skin features a 2-column feature, where the left column redirects you back to the main page, while the right column is where blog information is placed.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I have also improved indentation of the files when the site is being built, by using jekyll-tidy. The downside is that it only supports indentation with 2 spaces instead of 4. But atleast the source code will now be readable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Diary" /></entry><entry><title type="html">02.05 - 02.08: Summary</title><link href="/entry/4" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="02.05 - 02.08: Summary" /><published>2021-02-08T04:25:11+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-08T04:25:11+00:00</updated><id>/entry/4</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/4">&lt;p&gt;Good morning.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I wasn't able to write entries on the remaining days last week, since the computer I was using was broken -_-. And since I was planning to create a new update for the website (mostly styling updates), I had no choice but to move the update.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I was also able to realise that I still have many elements left to style properly, but I will work on that to another day, since I still have a lot of things left to do.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Now that the computer is fixed already, I was finally able to start working on the update, and I was able to improve my osu! skills a bit as well (on Standard mode).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Diary" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Ranking up!</title><link href="/entry/3" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ranking up!" /><published>2021-02-04T03:47:21+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-04T03:47:21+00:00</updated><id>/entry/3</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/3">&lt;figure class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2021/02/osu!taiko-profile.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Apologies on where the image's angle is f'ed up ; ;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
        &lt;/figure&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Since I don't really play Taiko regularly, my rank only increases by hundreds (but atleast I get to be on the top 50 leaderboards on some maps)&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I'm not really that good at Taiko since I usually keep missing notes on streams (unless there's a pattern), but since I have been &lt;a href=&quot;https://taiko.bui.pm&quot;&gt;playing on a website&lt;/a&gt; for a long time, I may improved my skills a bit, until I finally figured to play Taiko on my old osu! account instead.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I'm kinda impressed since I didn't expect to reach 5 digits (because like I said, I'm not really that good at Taiko), so might as well improve and if I can, I would try to reach 4 digits.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Gaming" /></entry><entry><title type="html">2021.02.02</title><link href="/entry/2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2021.02.02" /><published>2021-02-02T02:44:51+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-02T02:44:51+00:00</updated><id>/entry/2</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/2">&lt;figure class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.gifer.com/9TLY.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.gifer.com/9TLY.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Doing homework / coding 😶&lt;/figcaption&gt;
        &lt;/figure&gt;
        &lt;p class=&quot;center&quot;&gt;There is literally nothing to do nowadays other than to watch TV or surf in the internet.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Life" /></entry><entry><title type="html">First entry</title><link href="/entry/1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First entry" /><published>2021-02-01T10:46:58+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-01T10:46:58+00:00</updated><id>/entry/1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/entry/1">&lt;p&gt;Good evening.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Due to the creation of my own theme, my old blog will be deprecated, and will be replaced with a new one.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The newly recreated skin is based on a &lt;a href=&quot;https://factory.blog.naver.com/skin/Detail.nhn?itemSeq=48402985&amp;amp;categoryNo=&amp;amp;tagNo=#cb&quot;&gt;specific skin&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.naver.com&quot;&gt;Naver Blog&lt;/a&gt;, and since I am having problems registering on it, plus the user base is Korean, I decided to mimic the theme instead. Although it's not a perfect copy (since the skin is still work in progress), it already looks like a decent copy of the skin (atleast for me.)&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;And of course, I modified it to fit my preferences, such as adding Twemoji support on the skin and syntax highlighting to it.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I'm kinda surprised that it was seemingly easy to copy, considering that I am a bit of a noob in web design and double checking my code 😅&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;I also based the skin on other websites, such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://xenosium.com&quot;&gt;Xenosium&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://osu.ppy.sh&quot;&gt;osu! web&lt;/a&gt;, so you may find a bit of the elements similar to these websites (such as the font, and UI design).&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Anyway, I have a lot of things to do right now, so I might as well end this entry.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Shoto</name></author><category term="Diary" /></entry></feed>